

Contact







no 33 Jalan 8/28B, Seksyen 8, Fasa 2,43650, Bandar Baru Bangi.

Yourwebsite.com

Skills



MICROSOFT OFFICE

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

ADOBE ANIMATE

ADOBE PREMIER

Language









BAHASA

ENGLISH PROGRAMMING

Passions











WAN MUHAMMAD YUSRI WAN KAMARUDIN

MULTIMEDIA EXECUTIVE



Profile

Graphic Design with more than 4 years experience related with advertising for online including offline. Provided professional service with extensive experience with client. Experienced in various task, documentation, maintaining professional relationship with client and meet the requirement and deadline. Have a various computer skill and willing to learn new program or knowledge.Im able to adapt well to experience new environment. Im Seeking a position Graphic designer or related to develop or continue career growth in creative department. Thank you.



Work Experience

AEROSYNERGY SDN BHD / 2021-2022

MULTIMEDIA EXECUTIVE

Assisted in various project for providing all creative content that required specificly. Lead a small team to develop and Maintaining trading business that are now called arbag Collection. Responsible for all graphic content assisted with my team and their work. Provide report and company timeline for a future growth. im also handling for the costing, Report, Sustainability, Management, and Also Administration.

SONIXPRESS / 2020-2021

SENIOR CREATIVE DESIGNER

Provide all creative content for the company. Presenting concept visualization through sketches, drawing and illustrations. overseeing design change and improvement throughtout the development process. integrating technical and visual solution into a design concept. learning and understanding current trends within the scope of food delivery that are available in malaysia.

BTS PRODUCTION SDN BHD / 2019-2020

CREATIVE DESIGNER

maintain and manage every project required for the company responsible for every graphic material for marketing and presentation purpose, responsible for offline editing for every project required. handling client and also concept presentation before production process.

EMES SERVICES/ Aug 2018- Nov 2019

OPERATION MANAGER

Develop and improvice the company corporate identity to be more presentable and friendly to our client.develop a booking system for booking and managing car.our main concern is to create a self rental company that can handle

multiple client in one time.

AQ REKA SDN BHD/ Jan - Aug 2018

Graphic Designer

Develop and improvice the company corporate identity to be more presentable and friendly to our client.develop a booking system for booking and managing car.our main concern is to create a self rental company that can handle multiple client in one time.



Education

UNIVERSITY TECHNICAL MALAYSIA MELAKA / 2013-2018

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE (MEDIA INTERACTIVE)

KOLEJ MATRICULATION NEGERI SEMBILAN / 2011-2013

MATRICULATION CERTIFICATE

SMK JALAN TIGA / 2006-2010

PMR & SPM